Everyone and their exes are invited
The Wilde Wedding is a comedy, romance film directed by Damian Harris.
After a whirlwind courtship, retired movie star Eve Wilde prepares to marry
her fourth husband, the renowned English writer Harold Alcott.
Sparks soon begin to fly when Eve's first ex and other guests
arrive at her estate for a weekend get-together.
Eve Wilde, played by Glenn Close.
Laurence, played by John Malkovich.
Harold, played by Patrick Stewart.
Priscilla Jones, played by Minnie Driver.
Mackenzie Darling, played by Grace Van Patten.
Rory, played by Jack Davenport.
The Wilde Wedding is a 2017 romantic comedy film written and directed by Damian Harris,
starring Glenn Close, John Malkovich, Patrick Stewart, and Minnie Driver.
It received a limited theatrical release and a direct-to-video release,
beginning September 15, 2017, by Vertical Entertainment.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.